<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">TG WS Proxy</string>

    <!-- Main screen -->
    <string name="proxy_stopped">Proxy stopped</string>
    <string name="proxy_starting">Proxy starting…</string>
    <string name="proxy_running">Proxy running</string>
    <string name="proxy_restarting">Proxy restarting…</string>
    <string name="proxy_stopping">Proxy stopping…</string>
    <string name="btn_start">Connect</string>
    <string name="btn_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="btn_stopping">Stopping…</string>
    <string name="btn_restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="open_in_telegram">Open in Telegram</string>
    <string name="copy_link">Copy link</string>
    <string name="proxy_link">Proxy link</string>
    <string name="link_copied">Link copied</string>
    <string name="secret_copied">Secret copied</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="port_in_use_title">Proxy could not start</string>
    <string name="port_in_use_message">Local port %1$d is already in use. Stop the other app using it or select another port.</string>
    <string name="port_in_use_open_settings">Change port</string>

    <!-- Stats -->
    <string name="stats_traffic">Traffic</string>
    <string name="stats_connections">Connections</string>
    <string name="stats_total">Total</string>
    <string name="stats_active">Active</string>
    <string name="stats_ws">WS</string>
    <string name="stats_tcp_fallback">TCP</string>
    <string name="stats_cf_proxy">CF</string>
    <string name="stats_bad">Rejected</string>
    <string name="stats_ws_errors">WS err</string>
    <string name="rejected_warning_title">Old proxy entries in Telegram</string>
    <string name="rejected_warning_message">Many connections are arriving with incorrect proxy settings. This usually means Telegram still has old entries for this local proxy. Delete them, then add the current link again. This stops unnecessary reconnects, reduces battery use, and helps Telegram connect without delays.</string>
    <string name="stats_upload">Sent</string>
    <string name="stats_download">Recv</string>
    <string name="stats_pool">Pool</string>

    <!-- Settings screen -->
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_connection_options">Connection</string>
    <string name="settings_apply_notice">Settings are saved automatically. Connection changes apply when you leave this screen; a running proxy will restart.</string>
    <string name="settings_connection">Local proxy</string>
    <string name="settings_host">Listen address</string>
    <string name="settings_host_desc">Use 127.0.0.1 for this phone only. Use 0.0.0.0 only for access from your local network.</string>
    <string name="settings_port">Port</string>
    <string name="settings_secret">Telegram proxy secret</string>
    <string name="settings_secret_desc">After changing the secret, add the proxy to Telegram again.</string>
    <string name="settings_copy_secret">Copy Telegram secret</string>
    <string name="settings_regenerate_secret">Generate new secret</string>
    <string name="settings_regenerate_secret_title">Generate a new secret?</string>
    <string name="settings_regenerate_secret_warning">Telegram connections using the current proxy link will stop working. You will need to add the proxy to Telegram again.</string>
    <string name="settings_regenerate_secret_confirm">Generate</string>
    <string name="settings_dc_section">Direct WebSocket targets</string>
    <string name="settings_dc_hint">Format: DC:IP (one per line)\nExample: 2:149.154.167.220</string>
    <string name="settings_dc_description">Advanced setting. Each line assigns a direct WebSocket target to a Telegram datacenter. Remove a line to use an enabled fallback route.</string>
    <string name="settings_auto_optimize">Configure connection automatically</string>
    <string name="settings_auto_optimize_desc">Chooses routes and safe connection defaults. Turn this off to configure the options below manually.</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_enable">Use Cloudflare fallback</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_enable_desc">Adds an alternate route when direct connections are blocked or unreliable.</string>
    <string name="settings_route_priority">Route order</string>
    <string name="settings_route_direct">Try WebSocket first</string>
    <string name="settings_route_direct_desc">WebSocket → Cloudflare → TCP. Recommended for most networks.</string>
    <string name="settings_route_direct_tcp_desc">WebSocket → TCP → Cloudflare. Prefers direct routes when possible.</string>
    <string name="settings_route_cf">Try Cloudflare first</string>
    <string name="settings_route_cf_desc">Cloudflare → WebSocket → TCP. Try this if Telegram media does not load.</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_priority">After WebSocket fails, try Cloudflare before TCP</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_priority_desc">When off, TCP is tried before Cloudflare.</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_custom_domain">Use only a custom Cloudflare domain</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_custom_domain_desc">Replaces the shared domain list with this domain. Use it only when shared domains are consistently unavailable.</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_domain_label">Domain</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_test">Test and select a domain</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_test_desc">Tests available domains against Telegram datacenters and selects the fastest working one for the current proxy run.</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_testing">Testing…</string>
    <string name="settings_perf_section">Connection tuning</string>
    <string name="settings_perf_description">Advanced settings. Defaults suit most devices; change one value at a time when troubleshooting.</string>
    <string name="settings_buf_size">Buffer size (KB)</string>
    <string name="settings_pool_size">Prepared WebSocket connections</string>
    <string name="settings_background">Power usage</string>
    <string name="settings_background_desc">Choose the balance between lower battery use and reliable background connections.</string>
    <string name="settings_keep_cpu_awake">Keep device awake</string>
    <string name="settings_keep_cpu_awake_desc">Prevents deep sleep for the most reliable screen-off operation. Turning it off reduces idle power use.</string>
    <string name="settings_preconnect_ws">Prepare WebSocket connections</string>
    <string name="settings_preconnect_ws_desc">Keeps direct connections ready for faster startup. When off, no prepared connections are used; the saved manual pool size is preserved.</string>
    <string name="settings_ws_ping_interval">WebSocket keepalive interval</string>
    <string name="settings_ws_ping_interval_desc">Longer intervals reduce radio wakeups but can make idle connections less reliable.</string>
    <string name="settings_route_probes">Check routes after startup and network changes</string>
    <string name="settings_route_probes_desc">Tests direct WebSocket, Cloudflare, and TCP to detect working routes.</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_refresh">Refresh shared Cloudflare domains</string>
    <string name="settings_cf_refresh_desc">Updates the shared domain list in the background. Built-in domains remain available when disabled.</string>
    <string name="settings_interface">Interface</string>
    <string name="settings_notification_traffic">Show traffic in the service notification</string>
    <string name="settings_notification_traffic_desc">Shows and refreshes the traffic counter every 5 seconds. When disabled, traffic is not shown and no periodic notification updates run.</string>
    <string name="settings_seconds_short">%1$d s</string>
    <string name="settings_theme">Appearance</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_mode">Theme</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_system">System</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_light">Light</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="settings_dynamic_color">Adaptive colors</string>
    <string name="settings_dynamic_color_desc">Use the device Material You palette</string>
    <string name="settings_support">Support and diagnostics</string>
    <string name="settings_connection_log">Connection log</string>
    <string name="settings_connection_log_desc">View live connection events and create a diagnostic report.</string>
    <string name="settings_detailed_stats">Show detailed statistics on the main screen</string>
    <string name="settings_detailed_stats_desc">Displays connection, route, pool, and error counters.</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_start">Start diagnostics</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_stop">Finish diagnostics</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_controls">Connection diagnostics</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_report_title">Connection diagnostics</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_active_title">Diagnostics enabled</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_recording_main">Diagnostics recording is active</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_start_instructions">Use diagnostics when Telegram cannot connect, media does not load, or the proxy is unstable. Start diagnostics, reproduce the problem in Telegram, then return here and finish.</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_active_instructions">Return to Telegram and reproduce the problem. When finished, come back here, finish diagnostics, and share the report from the top bar.</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_report_note">The report keeps the latest 4 MB of technical connection events. Message and media contents and the proxy secret are not recorded.</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_continue_background">Continue in background</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_export">Share report</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_clear">Delete saved report</string>
    <string name="diagnostics_export_failed">Unable to share diagnostic report</string>

    <!-- Validation errors -->
    <string name="validation_host_format">Enter a valid IP address or hostname</string>
    <string name="validation_port_range">Port must be between 1 and 65535</string>
    <string name="validation_secret_format">Secret must contain 32 hexadecimal characters</string>
    <string name="validation_dc_format">Use DC:IP with DC 1–5 or 203, one per line</string>
    <string name="validation_domain_format">Enter a valid domain name</string>
    <string name="validation_buffer_range">Buffer must be between 4 and 4096 KB</string>
    <string name="validation_pool_range">Pool size must be between 0 and 16</string>

    <!-- Notification -->
    <string name="notification_channel_name">Proxy service</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_desc">Shows proxy status</string>
    <string name="notification_advice_channel_name">Connection recommendations</string>
    <string name="notification_advice_channel_desc">Shows route recommendations when automatic connection mode is off</string>
    <string name="notification_title" translatable="false">TG WS Proxy</string>
    <string name="notification_running">Traffic: %1$s</string>
    <string name="notification_running_no_traffic">Proxy is running</string>
    <string name="notification_restarting">Restarting proxy…</string>
    <string name="notification_restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="notification_stop">Stop</string>

    <!-- Quick Settings tile -->
    <string name="tile_active">Running</string>
    <string name="tile_inactive">Stopped</string>
    <string name="runtime_route">Route: %1$s</string>

    <!-- CF proxy test -->
    <string name="cf_test_success">DC%1$d: OK (%2$dms)</string>
    <string name="cf_test_fail">DC%1$d: Error</string>
    <string name="cf_test_best">Best domain: %1$s</string>
    <string name="cf_test_done">Test completed</string>
    <string name="cf_test_no_domains">CF proxy is disabled or no domains are available</string>

    <!-- Common UI -->
    <string name="navigate_back">Back</string>
    <string name="more_options">More options</string>
    <string name="telegram_not_found">Telegram is not installed</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_required">Notification permission is required for the foreground service</string>
    <string name="update_check_now">Check for updates</string>
    <string name="update_checking">Checking for updates…</string>
    <string name="update_up_to_date">You have the latest version</string>
    <string name="update_check_failed">Could not check for updates</string>
    <string name="update_available_title">Update available</string>
    <string name="update_available_version">Version %1$s is available</string>
    <string name="update_install">Update</string>
    <string name="update_download_install">Download and install</string>
    <string name="update_open_release">Open release page</string>
    <string name="update_downloading">Downloading update…</string>
    <string name="update_open_failed">Unable to open the release page</string>
    <string name="update_download_failed">Unable to download or verify the update</string>
    <string name="update_install_failed">Unable to open the verified update installer</string>
    <string name="update_install_permission_required">Allow TG WS Proxy to install unknown apps, then tap Update again</string>
    <string name="update_install_permission_failed">Unable to open the install permission settings</string>
    <string name="dc_ip_label" translatable="false">DC:IP</string>
    <string name="github" translatable="false">GitHub</string>

    <!-- Event log -->
    <string name="log_title">Connection log</string>
    <string name="log_not_recording">Live events</string>
    <string name="log_empty">No connection events yet</string>
    <string name="connection_advice_title">Network recommendation</string>
    <string name="connection_advice_enable_cf">Direct connections repeatedly time out on this network. Cloudflare is recommended.</string>
    <string name="connection_advice_cf_first">Direct connections repeatedly time out while Cloudflare is stable. Cloudflare first is recommended.</string>
    <string name="connection_advice_direct_first">Cloudflare repeatedly fails while direct connections are stable. Direct connection first is recommended.</string>

    <!-- Help -->
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_intro">This guide describes how the proxy works, what each setting changes, and how to diagnose connection problems.</string>
    <string name="help_overview_title">How the app works</string>
    <string name="help_overview_text">Telegram connects to a local MTProto proxy on this device. The app reads the requested Telegram datacenter and forwards the encrypted connection through direct WebSocket, Cloudflare, or direct TCP. It performs lightweight route checks after startup and network changes. The active route order is shown on the main screen. Traffic contents are not decrypted by the interface or written to the connection log.</string>
    <string name="help_quick_start_title">Initial setup</string>
    <string name="help_quick_start_text">1. Start the proxy on the main screen.\n2. Tap “Open in Telegram.”\n3. Confirm the proxy in Telegram.\n4. Keep the service notification enabled.\n\nSettings are saved automatically. A running proxy restarts after leaving settings only when connection settings actually changed.</string>
    <string name="help_mode_title">Connection modes</string>
    <string name="help_mode_text">“Configure connection automatically” starts each proxy run and each new network with WebSocket → Cloudflare → TCP and safe connection defaults. If it temporarily selects Cloudflare → WebSocket → TCP, prepared direct WebSocket connections are disabled. If only one datacenter’s media route stops returning data, the app temporarily sends only that media route through Cloudflare. The active route order is shown on the main screen.\n\nTurn automatic configuration off to reveal manual routing options, Direct WebSocket targets, and Connection tuning directly below the switch. Manual values remain saved while automatic configuration is enabled. Settings are saved automatically; connection changes apply when you leave Settings and the running proxy restarts.</string>
    <string name="help_cf_title">Cloudflare settings</string>
    <string name="help_cf_text">These controls are available when automatic connection mode is off. “Use Cloudflare fallback” adds the alternate route. Route order selects WebSocket or Cloudflare first; the additional switch controls whether Cloudflare or TCP follows a failed WebSocket attempt.\n\n“Use only a custom Cloudflare domain” replaces the entire shared list. Use it only when shared domains are consistently unavailable. “Test and select a domain” checks available domains against Telegram datacenters. HTTP 429 means a shared domain reached its connection limit; the app temporarily skips it.</string>
    <string name="help_dc_title">Direct WebSocket targets</string>
    <string name="help_dc_text">These controls are available when “Automatic connection mode” is off. A DC:IP line enables direct WebSocket for one Telegram datacenter. Telegram selects the datacenter automatically; the app only selects its route. Removing a line makes that datacenter use Cloudflare or TCP instead. Leave the default list unchanged unless you are isolating a routing problem or following a support instruction.</string>
    <string name="help_advanced_title">Performance settings</string>
    <string name="help_advanced_text">These controls are available when “Automatic connection mode” is off. The pool keeps direct WebSocket connections ready to reduce startup delay. The buffer controls socket memory used during transfers. The default pool size and 256 KB buffer are suitable for most devices. Lower the pool only to reduce memory and connection usage. Do not increase these values without a measured reason.</string>
    <string name="help_battery_title">Power usage</string>
    <string name="help_battery_text">The Power usage section lets you balance lower battery use against background connection reliability. It contains independent controls for device sleep, prepared connections, keepalive packets, route checks, and shared Cloudflare-domain updates. “Keep device awake” gives the most reliable screen-off operation but prevents deep sleep. Disable it first when investigating high idle power use. If connections then stop with the screen off, enable it again or allow unrestricted background operation in Android settings. “Prepare WebSocket connections” reduces connection delay but retains idle sockets. Route checks and domain updates can be disabled independently; automatic routing can still react to failures from real Telegram sessions.\n\nThe WebSocket keepalive interval applies to idle active sessions. 30 seconds prioritizes reliability; 90 or 180 seconds reduces cellular radio wakeups, but some networks may close idle connections.</string>
    <string name="help_theme_title">Theme and appearance</string>
    <string name="help_theme_text">Choose System, Light, or Dark appearance. On Android 12 and newer, adaptive colors use the Material You palette generated from the device wallpaper. Appearance changes are applied and saved automatically.</string>
    <string name="help_log_title">Connection log</string>
    <string name="help_log_text">The screen shows the latest 300 connection events from memory. To prepare a report, open Connection diagnostics, tap “Start diagnostics,” reproduce the problem in Telegram, return here, and tap “Finish diagnostics.” Then use “Share report” in the top bar.\n\nDiagnostics continues until manually finished and keeps approximately 4 MB of the latest technical events, discarding the oldest first. Message and media contents and the proxy secret are not recorded. Exported reports also redact proxy links and IP addresses. Saved files expire after 7 days. Deleting a saved report does not clear the events shown on screen.</string>
    <string name="help_troubleshooting_title">Troubleshooting</string>
    <string name="help_troubleshooting_text">Media does not load in automatic mode: keep the download open while the app detects the stalled media connection and retries that datacenter through Cloudflare.\n\nMedia does not load in manual mode: select “Try Cloudflare first” and leave Settings to apply the change.\n\nCloudflare fails: turn automatic mode off, test the domains, and look for HTTP 429 in the connection log.\n\nConnections stop with the screen off: allow background operation and disable battery optimization for the app.\n\nProblem persists: start Connection diagnostics, reproduce the issue, finish diagnostics, and share the report.</string>
    <string name="help_background_title">Background operation</string>
    <string name="help_background_text">Keep the foreground-service notification enabled. Some Android vendors may still restrict background networking; exclude the app from battery optimization if connections stop when the screen is off. If “Keep device awake” is off, enable it again before investigating other screen-off failures.</string>

    <!-- About screen -->
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string name="about_version">Version %1$s (%2$d)</string>
    <string name="about_description">An on-device MTProto proxy for Telegram with WebSocket transport and automatic Cloudflare/TCP fallback.</string>
    <string name="about_local_title">Local and private</string>
    <string name="about_local_text">Runs entirely on your device without root, an account, ads, or analytics.</string>
    <string name="about_transport_title">Resilient transport</string>
    <string name="about_transport_text">Uses pooled TLS WebSocket connections with Cloudflare and direct TCP fallback.</string>
    <string name="about_background_title">Built for background use</string>
    <string name="about_background_text">Includes a foreground service, notification controls, Quick Settings tile, and live statistics.</string>
    <string name="about_source_code">Source code</string>
    <string name="about_license">MIT License</string>
    <string name="about_based_on">Inspired by tg-ws-proxy by Flowseal. This Android implementation is developed independently.</string>
    <string name="about_flowseal_project">Original Flowseal project</string>
</resources>
